What are you looking at?
Nothing.
I just lost my husband.
I am a young widow.
I don't have time to play
romantic games with you.
Drop your little schemes.
Why don't you two stay inside a bit longer?
Yes, yes, yes.
I will deal with it seriously.
Okay.
See, I told you my intel was reliable.
I watched them go in with my own eyes.
If you saw them, why didn't you stop them?
I saw that little Taoist nun was there.
I was afraid Lord Huo would make things difficult for you later.
That's true.
How did they end up there?
After you, Madam.
Boss Ye.
What brings you here?
What kind of business do you need to handle?
The customer who just left,
what business was he doing?
I'm sorry, Boss Ye.
You know our rules.
I understand.
Where is my safe?
Number three.
Come this way.
What does number three mean, Young Master?
Don't speak.
You're just a servant. Stop talking.
After you, Madam.
Please.
You,
stay here.
Yes, Young Master.
We have big things to do.
Come, Mr. Ye.
This way.
This way, please.
Madam.
The diamond necklace my mom gave me,
I put it in the safe.
Where is the necklace?
I remember now.
It doesn't seem to be in the safe.
Let's hurry up and go then.
I just remembered something.
We need to go now.
We'll be back later.
It's okay.
Let's go.
Go.
Bai Xianming wants to deposit money into this bank.
What do these letters mean?
This is William Ray.
It's an English name.
Translated, this Ray can be the Chinese surname Lei.
Then it must be Lei Lie.
That means,
after Bai Xianming receives
the remittance from the hospital every month,
he transfers it to Lei Lie.
We have to find a way to locate this person.
Ningning,
you'll have to bear with it for a bit.
That bastard is named William Ray.
He said he is in England,
has a big house,
fifty acres wide.
And he also opened a red wine...
You know.
Red wine.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So he hopes I can fund his return to England.
Put it this way.
Miss.
Get to the point.
The point is,
I gave him some money,
and then, boom,
he disappeared.
This is considered fraud.
Exactly.
You can.
I promise you.
I, Zhou Wei, promise you.
I will definitely help you find the scammer.
Mr. Ye,
our William Firm
is the most famous firm in the British Empire.
May I ask, Mr. Ye,
what business you plan to cooperate with us on?
Could you give me a copy
of the detailed information about William Firm
to look at?
Please wait a moment.
I'll go get it now.
This William Lei is not Lei Lie,
but Lei Lie's son who is studying in the UK,
Lei Zijun.
In this William Firm,
Lei Zijun also has shares.
All the banned drugs are smuggled by William Firm
through a British company
called Black Mass.
With this evidence,
Lei Lie is doomed.
Superintendent Li,
can I apply for an arrest warrant now?
The evidence is conclusive.
Let's move.
Search the place.
Sir, we didn't find him.
Bai Xianming escaped.
To the concession.
Li Chengrui.
Why are you here?
Where is he?
He escaped.
After him!
I told you before,
I'm always ready for your visit.
All right.
Then come with us.
Detective Jiang.
You are using Hanyang rifles.
My brothers are using
imported German Mausers.
If the guns go off,
who do you think has the advantage?
Bullets
are blind.
No matter what,
I must take you away today.
That depends on whether
you have what it takes.
All of you, step outside.
You guys step outside too.
If Detective Jiang can beat me today,
I'll go with her.
No one is to stop us.
You step outside too.
No.
Even though I don't have a gun,
I can stay as a witness.
Excuse me.
Hurry up.
If he gets away,
I won't spare you, you know?
Hurry up.
Hurry.
Iron Sand Palm.
You killed Zheng Kun.
Cut the crap.
Tell me,
why didn't you set up a checkpoint for me?
I did.
You might not understand how checkpoints work.
Look at all these intersections.
We don't have enough police force.
You'd better stay far away later.
If there's any danger,
I won't be able to explain it to Master Huo.
Bai Xianming!
Chase him!
Stop! Stop!
Who told you to shoot?
My lady,
didn't you say
not to let him step into the concession?
You...
Hos...
pital.
What did you say?
Take him to the hospital, hurry!
Doctor, how is his condition?
He is out of danger,
but the patient is still very weak.
Okay.
Senior Sister.
Professor Bai is dead.
How did he die?
Chief Lei,
for you to end up here,
this matter
is no small one.
If I don't meet a good end today,
I'm afraid neither of us will end up well.
Say what you should say,
but for what you shouldn't,
you must think twice.
Detective Jiang,
why are you here?
Bai Xianming is dead.
I just wanted to injure him.
I didn't expect to kill him.
I have to come keep an eye on Lei Lie.
If he dies,
this case will be even harder to solve.
Our prison,
even if not impregnable,
wouldn't just let outsiders in.
Superintendent Li,
how about I interrogate him?
Okay.
Lei Lie.
The evidence is conclusive now.
You'd better confess.
Evidence?
What evidence?
If you had evidence, why would you ask me?
Lei Lie.
Don't be too arrogant.
All right.
Stop wasting time.
You're too green.
You can't do anything to me.
Since Chief Lei is so confident,
why are you still sitting here?
Remember this.
My dad and Jinwen won't die in vain.
No.
Why do you keep picking on me?
Their deaths have nothing to do with me.
If you don't confess clearly today,
you won't walk out of this door.
Do you dare to make a bet with me?
Bet on what?
Of course, bet that I
will walk out of here safely.